[♪♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
This is my little brother,
George.
[GRUNTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
[SNORTS]
And this is Daddy Pig.
[GRUNTS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Peppa Pig.
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READS ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
It is raining today,
So, Peppa and George
cannot play outside.
[SNORTS]
Daddy, it stopped raining.
Can we go out to play?
Ha, ha. All right,
run along, you two.
[BOTH SNORT, LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
[SPLASHES]
NARRATOR:
Peppa loves jumping
in muddy puddles!
[GRUNTS]
I love muddy puddles.
[LAUGHS]
[SNORTS]
MOMMY PIG: Peppa!
If you jump
in muddy puddles,
you must
wear your boots.
Sorry, Mommy.
[♪♪♪]
[GIGGLES]
NARRATOR:
George likes to jump
in muddy puddles too.
[SPLASHING]
[GRUNTS]
George!
If you jump
in muddy puddles,
you must wear your boots!
NARRATOR:
Peppa likes to look after
her little brother, George.
[♪♪♪]
[GIGGLING, GRUNTING]
George, let's find
some more puddles.
[♪♪♪]
[SPLASHING, LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George
are having a lot of fun.
Peppa has found
a little puddle.
[SLOSHES]
George has found
a big puddle.
[SLOSHING]
[BOTH SLOSHING]
[BOTH PANTING]
[GIGGLES]
Look, George!
There's a really
big puddle!
NARRATOR:
George wants to jump into
the big puddle first.
Stop, George!
I must check if
it's safe for you.
[SLOSHES]
Good! It is
safe for you.
[CRYING]
Sorry, George.
It's only mud.
[LAUGHS]
[SLOSHES]
[GRUNTING, LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George love jumping
in muddy puddles.
[SLOSHING]
[SNORTS]
Come on, George!
Let's go and show Daddy!
[♪♪♪]
[GIGGLING]
[SNORTS]
Goodness me!
Daddy! Daddy!
Guess what
we've been doing?
Let me think... Have you been
watching television?
No, no, Daddy.
Have you just
had a bath?
[BOTH LAUGH]
No! No!
I know!
You've been jumping
in muddy puddles!
Yes, yes, Daddy!
We've been jumping
in muddy puddles!
Ho, ho. And look at
the mess you're in.
Ooh.
Oh, well,
it's only mud.
Let's clean up quickly,
before Mommy sees the mess.
Daddy, when
we've cleaned up,
will you and Mommy
come and play too?
Yes, we can all
play in the garden.
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA & GEORGE GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George
are wearing their boots.
Mommy and Daddy
NARRATOR:
Peppa loves jumping up and down
in muddy puddles.
[LAUGHING]
Everyone loves jumping up
and down in muddy puddles.
[SPLASHING, LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
[ALL GASP]
Oh, Daddy Pig,
look at the mess you're in.
It's only mud.
[GRUNTS, LAUGHS]
[♪♪♪]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[BIRDS TWEETING]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READS ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
George's favorite toy
is Mr. Dinosaur.
[GRUNTS]
Dine-Saw!
[GIGGLES]
NARRATOR:
George loves Mr. Dinosaur.
Grrr!
[LAUGHS, GRUNTS]
NARRATOR:
Sometimes George likes to scare
Peppa with Mr. Dinosaur.
Grrr!
Eeek! Too scary!
[LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
At suppertime, Mr. Dinosaur
sits next to George.
[BURPS]
MOMMY PIG: I beg your pardon!
Was that you, George,
or was it Mr. Dinosaur?
Dine-Saw!
[BURPS]
[ALL LAUGH]
NARRATOR:
At bath time, George shares
his bath with Mr. Dinosaur.
[BUBBLES POP]
Grr!
Tee-hee-hee.
[GRUNTS]
Good night, Peppa.
[SNORTS]
Good night, Mommy!
Good night, George.
And good night,
Mr. Dinosaur.
[GRUNTS]
Grr!
NARRATOR:
When George goes to bed,
Mr. Dinosaur
is tucked up with him.
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
George's favorite game
is throwing Mr. Dinosaur
up in the air...
Whee!
NARRATOR:
...and catching him
when he falls back down.
Whee!
[GIGGLES, SNORTS]
Wee!
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
NARRATOR:
Peppa and Daddy Pig
are playing draughts.
[LAUGHING]
I win, Daddy!
Ha, ha!
Oh. Well done, Peppa.
[CRYING]
George?
[CONTINUES CRYING]
George, what's the matter?
Dine-Saw...
George, have you lost
Mr. Dinosaur?
[GRUNTS]
NARRATOR:
George has lost Mr. Dinosaur.
MOMMY PIG:
Don't worry, George.
We'll find Mr. Dinosaur.
It's a job for a detective.
Daddy, what is
a de-tech-tiff?
A detective
is a very
important person,
who is good
at finding things.
Me! Me!
I'm good at finding things!
All right!
Peppa is the detective!
George. I am
the de-tech-tiff,
[GRUNTS]
I will help you find
Mr. Dinosaur.
Maybe the detective should ask
George some simple questions.
George?
Where's Mr. Dinosaur?
[SOBS]
NARRATOR:
George does not know
where Mr. Dinosaur is.
The detective could try
and guess where
Mr. Dinosaur might be.
I know!
I know where he is!
[GRUNTS, GIGGLES]
George always has Mr. Dinosaur
with him in the bath.
So Mr. Dinosaur
is in the bath!
NARRATOR:
Mr. Dinosaur
is not in the bath.
Oh. I know!
I know where
Mr. Dinosaur is! Hee-hee!
George always has Mr. Dinosaur
in his bed at night.
[GRUNTS]
So that's where he is!
NARRATOR:
Mr. Dinosaur is not
in George's bed.
Oh.
Maybe we should try
the garden.
Yes, the garden!
[SNORTS]
I was going to say that!
[♪♪♪]
Where is Mr. Dinosaur?
NARRATOR:
Mr. Dinosaur
is very hard to find.
Oh... Mr. Dinosaur
isn't anywhere!
George?
You do love to throw
Mr. Dinosaur in the air.
I wonder if this time
you threw Mr. Dinosaur
just a bit too high.
PEPPA:
There he is! There he is!
I saw him first!
[GRUNTS]
Well done, Peppa!
You really are
a very good detective!
[GRUNTS]
[GIGGLING]
[SNORTS]
Dine-Saw.
Grr!
NARRATOR:
George is so happy to have
Mr. Dinosaur back again.
Whee!
[BRANCHES RUSTLE]
[WHIMPERING]
Maybe it isn't
a good idea
to play with dinosaurs
near trees.
[GIGGLES]
[ALL LAUGH]
Dine-Saw!
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READS ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa is waiting for
her best friend, Suzy Sheep.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
Hello, Suzy!
Baa! Hello, Peppa.
NARRATOR:
Suzy Sheep has come to play
with Peppa.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
[GRUNTS]
[BLEATS]
NARRATOR:
Peppa loves Suzy.
Suzy loves Peppa.
They are best friends.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Peppa, why don't you and Suzy
go and play in your bedroom?
[SNORTS]
Yes, Mommy!
SUZY: Baa!
[PEPPA GRUNTS]
NARRATOR:
George wants to play too.
[GIRLS LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and Suzy love playing
in Peppa's bedroom.
So does George.
[LAUGHS, GRUNTS]
No, George.
This game is just
for big girls.
[SNORTS]
Go and play with
your own toys.
NARRATOR:
Peppa and Suzy want
to play on their own.
I'm a tiny little
fairy princess.
[GRUNTS]
[SNORTS, GRUNTS]
[GIGGLES]
[GRUNTS]
I'm going to wave
my magic wand, ha, ha!
And turn you into
a frog!
[SCREAMS]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
George doesn't like
playing on his own.
[GIRLS LAUGHING, SHOUTING]
NARRATOR:
George wants to play too.
No, George!
I'm playing with Suzy.
You have to play
somewhere else.
NARRATOR:
George wants to play with
Peppa. He feels a bit lonely.
George, I need some help!
I'm making
chocolate chip cookies!
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
Someone needs to
lick out the bowl.
[GRUNTS, LAUGHS]
[SLURPING]
NARRATOR: George likes
helping Mommy make cookies.
[GIRLS GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
But he likes playing
with Peppa more.
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS, LAUGHS]
Baa, I want to be a nurse!
[SNORTS]
I want to be a doctor.
But who's gonna be
the sick person?
[SLURPS]
PEPPA: George!
[GRUNTS, LAUGHS]
[BOTH GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and Suzie love playing
doctors and nurses.
So does George.
Peppa listens
to George's chest.
Now, George,
take a big breath in...
then cough.
[INHALES, COUGHS]
Hmm, I think your heart's
a bit loose.
I'll put a plaster on it.
Baa!
Open wide, please.
NARRATOR:
Suzy takes
George's temperature.
Oh dear,
you're very, very hot.
I think you have to stay
in bed for three years.
[GIGGLES]
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig has come
to find George.
[GRUNTS]
Oh no!
What's wrong with George?
Don't worry, Daddy.
It's only a game.
George is our patient.
Oh, I see.
Can the patient have
a visitor?
Just for a little while.
He might get tired.
PEPPA & SUZY:
Cookies!
[SNORTS]
Yes, they're for George.
They're his medicine
to make him feel better.
[GRUNTS, LAUGHS]
[CRUNCHES]
Um, excuse me, Doctor,
can you help me?
I have a sore tummy.
Hee, hee, that tickles!
[SNORTS]
[GURGLING]
[GIGGLES, SNORTS]
I can hear it rumbling.
I think you're hungry,
Daddy.
[GIGGLING]
Then I think I need lots of
cookies to make me better.
[GIRLS GIGGLING]
[GRUNTS]
And me!
[SNORTS]
And me! Baa!
[ALL CRUNCHING, LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READS ONSCREEN TEXT]
[CAR ENGINE HUMMING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her family
are visiting
Granny Pig and Grandpa Pig.
[GIGGLING, SNORTING]
Granny Pig! Grandpa Pig!
[SNORTS]
Ganggy Ig! Baba Ig!
Hello, my little ones.
Come inside.
We have a surprise.
What is it?
We have a new pet.
Can you guess
what it is?
[GRUNTS]
Dine-saw?
[SNORTS, LAUGHS]
No, it's not a dinosaur.
[SNORTS]
Come and see.
[SQUAWKS]
NARRATOR:
Granny Pig and Grandpa Pig
have a pet parrot.
Peppa, George,
this is our pet parrot.
[SNORTS]
She's called Polly.
Pretty Polly.
[SQUAWKS]
Ooh.
Wow!
I'm a clever parrot.
[SQUAWKS]
[BOTH GIGGLE]
[SNORTS]
Mommy,
why does Polly copy
everything that Granny says?
[SNORTS]
That's what parrots
do.
I'll show you.
Hello, Polly.
What a sweet
little parrot!
[ALL LAUGH]
[SNORTS]
Come on everyone,
teatime!
Peppa, George. Come on!
There's chocolate cake!
[SNORTS]
Coming, Granny!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George love
eating chocolate cake.
But today,
they are in a hurry
to get back and play
with Polly Parrot.
[SLURPING]
Finished!
[SLURPS, GRUNTS]
[LAUGHS, GRUNTS]
What noisy little ones you are!
PEPPA: Granny,
[SNORTS]
please can we
leave the table,
and go and see
Polly Parrot?
Are you sure you've completely
finished your cake?
Off you go then.
Hooray!
[LAUGHING, GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪]
George, say something
to Polly.
NARRATOR:
George is a little bit shy.
[GRUNTS]
Hello.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[SQUAWKING, LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George
are really enjoying
playing with Polly Parrot.
I'm Peppa Pig!
[GIGGLES]
[GRUNTS]
George, say something!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are
pretending to be parrots.
[SNORTING, GIGGLING]
I'm Polly Parrot.
[GRUNTS]
Hee-hee-hee.
NARRATOR:
Peppa is thinking of something
else to say to Polly Parrot.
I'm a noisy parrot!
[SNORTS]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[SQUAWKING, LAUGHING]
Peppa, George, have you been
playing with Polly?
Yes, Granny.
[GRUNTS]
Polly is such a sweet parrot.
Yes, Granny.
I'm a clever parrot.
I'm a noisy parrot!
[SNORTS]
[LAUGHS]
[ALL GASP]
Oh, my word!
[LAUGHS, SNORTS]
[SNORTS, LAUGHS]
[LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
[LAUGHING, SQUAWKING]
[GIGGLING]
PEPPA:
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING, GIGGLING]
[GRUNTING]